Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 4 and District 4 Locals, 1935-1991 UE.4.1.4
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 4 Locals, 2.
  - Local 455
    - Local 455 Organization, October 22, 1942-January 15, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 124)
      - Jack McDonough to James Matles, October 22, 1942; 1.
      - McDonough to Julius Emspak, October 24, 1942; 2.
      - Emspak to W.R. Burrows, October 29, 1942; 3.
      - Membership Resolution, November 6, 1942; 4.
      - Robert Dixon Telegram to Emspak, January 15, 1943; 5.
    - Local 455 Incentive and Wildcat Strike, December 29, 1942-April 21, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 125)
      - Robert Dixon to Julius Emspak, December 29, 1942; 1.
      - Emspak to Dixon, January 11, 1943; 2.
      - P. Paxton to W.R. Burrows, February 6, 1943; 3.
      - Walter Barry to Emspak, March 8, 1943; 4.
      - Leo Jandreau to Henery Rhine, August 19, 1943; 5.
      - Barry to Emspak, April 21, 1943; 6.
    - Local 455 Check-off, June 1-7, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 126)
      - Julius Emspak to Walter Barry, June 1, 1945; 1.
      - James Lustig to Emspak, June 7, 1945; 2.
    - Local 455 Strike, January 15-June 19, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 127)
      - Report of Strike, January 15, 1946; 1.
      - Bertha Fielding to UE, June 17, 1946; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to James McLeish, June 19, 1946; 3.
    - Local 455 UE News, January 31-February 21, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 128)
      - Jack Spain to Julius Emspak, January 31, 1950; 1.
      - Emma Memo to Christine, February 8, 1950; 2.
      - James Matles to Walter Mugford, February 21, 1950; 3.
    - Local 455 Correspondence, April 16, 1943-February 8, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 129)
      - Julius Emspak to John McDonough Regarding Per Capita, April 16, 1943; 1.
      - Leo Jandreau to Henry Rhine Regarding National Labor Relations Board Bargaining Unit, February 7, 1944; 2.
      - Jandreau to Rhine Regarding Officers, October 11, 1943; 3.
      - Lelia Rottkamp to Emspak Regarding Dues, February 8, 1945; 4.
  - Local 456
    - Local 456 Constitution, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 130)
    - Local 456 Officers Lists, April 19, 1944-September 7, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 131)
    - Local 456 Officers Lists, October 26, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 132)
    - Local 456 Membership Lists, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 133)
    - Local 456 Membership Minutes, October 4, 1947-March 23, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 134)
    - Local 456 Resolutions, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 135)
      - Resolution Regarding War Labor Board, 1944; 1-2.
      - Resolution Regarding Hours, 1944; 3.
      - Resolution Regarding Incentive Pay with Herman Reichbach Letter to Edward Matthews, 1944; 4.
    - Local 456 Incoming Correspondence, February 1, 1943-February 24, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 136)
      - Janet Barish to Edward Wiese Regarding Strikes, February 24, 1956; 1.
      - Fred D'Avila to Anthony Longo Regarding Radio Broadcasts, August 2, 1949; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to Herbert Hoffmann Regarding Finances, February 1, 1943; 3.
      - Emspak to Hugh Finne Regarding Per Capita, December 31, 1943; 4.
      - Emspak to Philip Hendel Regarding Finances, February 18, 1944; 5.
      - Emspak to Lawrence Jones Regarding Dues, February 28, 1945; 6.
      - Emspak to Harry Simms Regarding Strike, April 30-May 15, 1946; 7-8.
      - Emspak to Thomas Scanlon Regarding Finances, July 17, 1946; 9.
      - Emspak to George Miller Regarding Finances, December 11, 1946; 10.
      - Emspak to Longo Regarding Political Action Committee, December 10, 1947; 11.
      - Emspak to Michael Balbo Regarding PAC, March 24, 1948; 12.
      - Emspak to Wiese Regarding Finances, June 10, 1948; 13.
      - Emspak to Wiese Regarding Fighting Fund, October 22, 1951; 14.
      - Emspak to Wiese Regarding Per Capita, June 18, 1952; 15.
      - Emspak to Wiese Regarding Strike, June 22-December 2, 1955; 16-17.
      - Emspak to Wiese Regarding Strike with December 12, 1955, Emspak Letter to William Rossmore; December 13, 1955, Emspak Letter to Morton Stavis; and January 12, 1956, Emspak Letter to Wiese, December 19, 1955; 18.
      - Emspak to Wiese Regarding Strike, January 12-February 15, 1956; 19-23.
      - Emspak to Wiese Regarding Finances, January 25, 1956; 24.
    - Local 456 Incoming Correspondence, August 6, 1948-March 29, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 137)
      - Julius Emspak to Edward Wiese Regarding Strike, February 16-March 29, 1956; 1-8.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Wiese Regarding Annual Dance, January 23, 1951; 9.
      - Kate Heck to Michael Balbo Regarding District Executive Board, August 6, 1948; 10.
    - Local 456 Incoming Correspondence, April 6, 1948-December 20, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 138)
      - James Matles to Mel Kennedy Regarding Organization, November 13, 1952; 1.
      - Matles to Hal Kennedy Regarding Organization, November 13, 1952; 2.
      - Matles to Edward Wiese Regarding Dues Check-off, March 30, 1953; 3.
      - Matles to Wiese, October 5, 1956; 4.
      - Matles to Herman Reichbach Regarding Finances, October 5, 1956; 5.
      - Matles to Raymond Bucci Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, December 20, 1956; 6.
      - James McLeish Telegram to George Sabades Regarding Factionalism, April 6, 1948; 7.
      - McLeish to Brother or Sister Regarding Factionalism, May 3, 1948; 8.
      - McLeish to Thomas Bracken Regarding Factionalism, June 9, 1848; 9.
      - McLeish to Sabados Regarding Factionalism, June, 9, 1948; 10.
      - McLeish to Bracken Regarding Factionalism, August 5, 1948; 11.
      - McLeish to Local 456 President Regarding Factionalism, 1948; 12.
      - Russ Nixon to Michael Balbo Regarding Political Action, May 12, 1948; 13.
    - Local 456 Outgoing Correspondence, January 28, 1944-August 28, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 139)
      - Michael Balbo to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Taft-Hartley, May 26, 1947; 1.
      - Balbo to Julius Emspak Regarding Veterans, January 29, 1948; 2.
      - Balbo to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, March 17, 1948; 3.
      - Balbo to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism, May 10, 1948; 4.
      - Balbo to James McLeish Regarding Factionalism, June 14-August 10, 1948; 5-7.
      - Balbo to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, June 14, 1949; 8.
      - Balbo to Fitzgerald Regarding Wages, October 19, 1949; 9.
      - Mark Campanelli to Emspak Regarding Finances, May 4, 1948; 10.
      - Ben Chwalk to James Matles Regarding Membership Meeting, March 28, 1951; 11.
      - Ralph Chappa to Emspak Regarding PAC, January 7, 1948; 12.
      - Bart Enright to Reynolds Regarding Factionalism, March 18, 1948; 13.
      - James French to UE Regarding Address Change, January 28, 1944; 14.
      - French to Emspak Regarding Organization, May 10, 1945; 15.
      - Philip Hendel to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 10, 1944; 16.
      - Lawrence Jones to Emspak Regarding Constitution, September 14, 1944; 17.
      - Jones to Emspak Regarding Veterans, February 19, 1945; 18.
      - Mel Kennedy to UE Regarding Per Capita, August 28, 1951; 19.
      - Anthony Longo to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 30-September 16, 1947; 20-21.
      - Longo Telegram to McLeish Regarding Constitution, April 6, 1948; 22.
      - Herman Reichbach to Edward Matthews Regarding 1944 UE Convention, August 10, 1944; 23.
    - Local 456 Outgoing Correspondence, April 2, 1946-February 28, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 140)
      - Thomas Scanton to David Scribner Regarding Hours, November 29, 1946; 1.
      - Scanton to Julius Emspak Regarding Public Rally, April 2, 1946; 2.
      - Scanton to James Matles Regarding Public Rally, April 2, 1946; 3.
      - Scanton Telegram to UE Regarding Public Rally, April 5, 1946; 4.
      - Scanton Telegram to Edward Matthews Regarding Strikes, May 14, 1946; 5.
      - Scanton to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 16, 1946; 6.
      - Scanton to Emspak Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations, November 7, 1946; 7.
      - Frank Shapiro to UE Regarding Constitution, April 7, 1949; 8.
      - Edward Wiese to UE Regarding Strike, January 19, 1949; 9.
      - Wiese to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 30, 1950; 10.
      - Wiese to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Annual Dance, January 10, 1951; 11.
      - Wiese to Emspak Regarding 1951 UE Convention, October 10, 1951; 12.
      - Wiese to David Ratner Regarding Finances, February 8, 1955; 13.
      - Wiese to Matles Regarding Membership Meeting, April 6, 1955; 14.
      - Wiese to Janet Barish Regarding Strikes, February 28, 1956; 15.
      - Executive Board to Local 456 Regarding Unemployment, November 22, 1948; 16.
    - Local 456 Finances, April 16, 1953-December 12, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 141)
      - James Matles to Edward Wiese Regarding Dues Check-off, April 16, 1953; 1.
      - Bill, December 12, 1955; 2.
    - Local 456 Factionalism, March 23-October 7, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 142)
      - Bart English to Sister, March 23, 1948; 1.
      - Report of Election Committee, March 1948; 2.
      - Petition, March 1948; 3.
      - Election Results, April 7, 1948; 4.
      - Michael Balbo to James McLeish, June 14, 1948; 5.
      - Executive Board Meeting, August 6, 1948; 6.
      - James McLeish to David Scribner, September 16, 1948; 7.
      - Scribner to McLeish, September 23, 1948; 8.
      - Memo with Petition, October 7, 1948; 9.
    - Local 456 Constitution, April 7-May 3, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 143)
      - Frank Shapiro to UE, April 7, 1949; 1.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to William Santora, April 11, 1949; 2.
      - Michael Balbo to Fitzgerald, May 3, 1949; 3.
    - Local 456 Per Capita, June 14-30, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 144)
      - Michael Balbo to Julius Emspak, June 14, 1949; 1.
      - Emspak to William Santora, June 30, 1949; 2.
    - Local 456 Strike Memos, December 14-19, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Local 456 Disbanding Finances, December 26, 1956-March 7, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Irv Levine to David Ratner, December 26, 1956; 1.
      - Ranter to Public Service Corporation, January 4, 1957; 2.
      - Ratner to New Jersey Bell, January 4, 1957; 3.
      - Ratner to Levine, January 10, 1957; 4.
      - Ratner to Public Service Electric, January 31-March 7, 1947; 5-6.
      - Irv to David, 7.
    - Local 456 Correspondence, April 8, 1943-October 4, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Contract Suppliement, April 8, 1943; 1.
      - Officers Salary Unit, April 27, 1945; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to New Jersey Bell Regarding Supplies, July 25, 1946; 3.
      - Walter Barry to James Matles Regarding Factionalism, January 2, 1947; 4.
      - John Gidney Telegram to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Taft-Hartley, May 27, 1947; 5.
      - William Santora Letter Regarding Unemployment Strikes, 6.
      - Michael Balbo to Emspak Regarding Political Action, January 24, 1949; 7.
      - Draft Resolution Regarding Foreign Policy, August 14, 1951; 8.
      - Emspak to James McLeish with October 10, 1951, Edward Wiese Letter to Emspak, October 22, 1951; 9.
      - Memo to Janet Regarding Organization, October 4, 1956; 10.
    - Local 456 Newspaper, 456 Bulletin (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Local 456 Leaflets, 1945-1955 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - "Dear Sister" Regarding Factionalism, March 23, 1945; 1.
      - Sixth Annual Dance, April 12, 1948; 2.
      - "The Facts Are" Regarding Wages, 1948; 3.
      - Sample Ballot, 1948; 4.
      - Advertising Contract with April 27, 1954, William Santora Letter to Julius Emspak, 5.
      - "Look Before You Leap" Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, 1955; 6.
      - "Pete Abbondi Dead", 1955; 7.
      - "Essington Fight Continues" Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, 1955; 8.
      - "Hold that Line" Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, 1955; 9.
      - "All Out" Regarding Officers, 10.
    - Local 456 Pamphlets, 1943-1956 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - First Annual Dance, May 29, 1943; 1.
      - Highlights of the Westinghouse Strike with April 20, 1956, Edward Wiese Letter to Brothers and Sisters, 2.
    - Local 456 Newspaper Clippings, August 23, 1943-August 27, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - "Reconversion Layoffs Cause Some Confusion," Jersey Journal, August 21, 1945; 1.
      - "Kellogg Firm Lays off Workers," Jersey Observer, August 22, 1945; 2.
      - "Workers Meet on Jobs at Westinghouse," Jersey Journal, August 23, 1943; 3.
      - "Westinghouse Employees Stop Work," Jersey Journal, August 23, 1945; 4.
      - "Westinghouse Expected to Layoff More," Jersey Observer, August 24, 1945; 5.
      - "War Manpower Commission Appeals to Employees," Daily News, August 24, 1945; 6.
      - "Confer on Dispute at Westinghouse," Jersey Journal, August 24, 1945; 7.
      - "Westinghouse Layoff Clash Closes Plant," Jersey Observer, August 24, 1945; 8.
      - "Westinghouse Employees Claim Lockout at Jersey City Plant," Hudson Dispatch, August 25, 1945; 9.
      - "Says Essex Plant Have No Dispute," Newark Sun, August 25, 1945; 10.
      - "Non-working Westinghouse Employees Claim Lockout," Jersey Journal, August 25, 1945; 11.
      - "Westinghouse to Resume Work," Hudson Dispatch, August 27, 1945; 12.
  - Local 460
    - Local 460 Incoming Correspondence, April 12-June 1, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Julius Emspak to Elizabeth Haggas Regarding Supplies, April 12, 1945; 1.
      - Emspak to Anna Beggan Regarding Finances, August 16, 1945; 2.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Haggas Regarding Organization, June 1, 1945; 3.
    - Local 460 Outgoing Correspondence, August 10-June 17, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Gladys Dalag to Janet Barish Regarding Finances, August 10, 1945; 1.
      - Florence Gerald to Barish Regarding Staff Finances, July 17, 1945; 2.
      - Betty Haggas to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Organization, May 28, 1845; 3.
    - Local 460 Finances, March 3, 1945-November 9, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Charter Supplies, March 3, 1945; 1.
      - Stamps, March 9, 1945; 2.
      - Ledger, 1945-1946; 3.
      - Receipt, November 9, 1951; 4.
    - Local 460 Organization, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Report of Local 460, 1945; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Doris Lewis, March 5, 1945; 2.
      - Emspak to James McLeish, March 5, 1945; 3.
      - Ralph Fasanella to Emspak, November 28, 1945; 4.
  - Local 475
    - Local 475 Officers Lists, June 22, 1939-July 1, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Lists, June 22, 1939-August 21, 1946; 1-3.
      - List with Rose Seider Letter to UE, July 1, 1949; 4.
    - Local 475 Officers Lists, August 16, 1949-April 5, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Local 475 Resolutions, June 1947 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - Resolution Regarding Congressional Committee on Un-American Activities with June 26, 1947, Janet Green Letter to Albert Fitzgerald, June 1947; 1.
      - Resolution Regarding Taft-Hartley Bill, June 1947; 2-3.
      - Resolution Regarding General Strike, June 1947; 4.
      - Resolution Regarding Civil Rights Congress, June 24, 1947; 5.
      - Resolution Regarding UE News with July 14, 1947, William Askew Letter to Fitzgerald, June 24, 1947; 6.
    - Local 475 Cliff Cameron Incoming Correspondence, August 21, 1946-September 7, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - Janet Barish Regarding Finances, March 24, 1948; 1.
      - William Cahn Regarding Newspaper, January 18, 1950; 2.
      - Joseph Dermody Regarding Employment, December 5, 1949; 3.
      - Julius Emspak Regarding Local 475 Merger with August 20, 1946, Emspak Letter to Federal Reserve Bank and August 16, 1946, Bernard Ades Letter to UE, August 21, 1946; 4.
      - Emspak Regarding Employment, September 26, 1946; 5.
      - Emspak Regarding Local 475 Outing, August 23, 1949; 6.
      - Emspak Regarding Local 475 Strikes, April 25, 1949; 7.
      - Emspak Regarding Local 475 Sklar Strike, May 5-19, 1950; 8-9.
      - Emspak Regarding Mailing List and UE News with April 2, 1951, John Euguene Letter to Emspak and Survey, April 9, 1951; 10.
      - Emspak Regarding Health with Emspak Letter to Serge Schwartz, September 14, 1953; 11.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, October 26, 1954-August 12, 1955; 12-16.
      - Emspak Regarding Local 475 International Projector Corporation Strike, September 7, 1955; 17.
    - Local 475 Cliff Cameron Incoming Correspondence, October 1, 1946-March 13, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      - Julius Emspak Regarding American Safety Razor Pensions with January 15, 1956, E.M. Goebber Letter to UE, January 19, 1956; 1.
      - Emspak Regarding Local 475 International Projector Corporation Strike and Per Capita, February 19, 1956; 2.
      - Emspak Regarding Local 475 IPC Strike and Finances, March 13, 1956; 3.
      - Emspak Regarding Local 475 IPC Strike and Per Capita, April 23, 1956; 4.
      - Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Local 475 Outing, August 23, 1949; 5.
      - James Matles Regarding Mailing List, October 1, 1946; 6.
      - Matles Regarding Annual Report, December 9, 1946; 7.
      - Matles Regarding Brooklyn Organization, February 7, 1947; 8.
      - Matles Regarding Staff Members, March 10, 1947; 9.
      - Matles Regarding Employment with March 23, 1947, Thomas Delaney Letter to Matles and March 12, 1947, Delaney Letter to Ernest DeMaio, March 28, 1947; 10.
      - Matles Regarding Employment, April 12, 1947; 11.
      - Matles Regarding Staff Members, May 7, 1947; 12.
      - Matles Regarding Factionalism, June 2, 1947; 13.
      - Matles Regarding Stewards, June 2, 1947; 14.
      - Matles Regarding Finances, June 27-September 5, 1947; 15-16.
      - Matles Regarding E.W. Bliss, September 18, 1947; 17.
      - Matles Regarding Sheran Mettalic and National Equipment Organization, March 18, 1948; 18.
      - Matles Regarding Lightmakers Manufacturing with October 26, 1945, Raymond Lizard Letter to UE, November 8, 1948; 19.
      - Matles Regarding Staff Members, November 20, 1948; 20.
      - Matles Regarding American Machine and Foundry Organization, February 14, 1949; 21.
    - Local 475 Cliff Cameron Incoming Correspondence, February 17, 1949-July 25, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - James Matles Regarding American Machine and Foundry Organization, February 17, 1949; 1.
      - Matles Regarding Finances, March 11, 1949; 2.
      - Matles Regarding Burndy Engineering, April 1, 1949; 3.
      - Matles Regarding Finances and Staff Members, July 7, 1949; 4.
      - Matles Regarding Finances, August 19, 1949; 5.
      - Matles Regarding Teamsters Inter-union Rivalry with Matles Letter to Max Short and September 13, 1949, Short Letter to UE, September 20, 1949; 6.
      - Matles Regarding Finances, September 28, 1949; 7.
      - Matles Regarding Non-Communist Affidavits, November 17, 1949; 8.
      - Matles Regarding Finances, December 27, 1949-March 21, 1950; 9-10.
      - Matles Regarding Local 475 American Safety Razor Strike, June 6, 1951; 11.
      - Matles Regarding Annual Report, January 29, 1952; 12.
      - Matles Regarding Strike Fund, October 27, 1952; 13.
      - Matles Regarding International Harvester Strikes, December 5, 1952; 14.
      - Matles Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry with News Clipping, January 29, 1953; 15.
      - Matles Regarding Finances, August 23, 1954; 16.
      - Matles Regarding Local 932, October 13, 1954; 17.
      - Matles Regarding Staunton American Safety Razor with December 29, 1954, Matles Memo to David Ratner and November 23, 1954, Ben Memo to Ratner, November 22, 1954; 18.
      - Matles Regarding Staunton American Safety Razor, November 22, 1954; 19.
      - Matles Regarding IUE and United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, July 25, 1955; 20.
    - Local 475 Cliff Cameron Incoming Correspondence, September 25, 1946-April 25, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - James Matles Regarding Burndy Organization, November 9, 1955; 1.
      - Matles Regarding Local 107 Westinghouse Strike, April 25, 1956; 2.
      - Russ Nixon Regarding Local 475 Outing, August 31, 1951; 3.
      - Ben Riskin Regarding Arma Organization, September 25, 1946; 4.
    - Local 475 Cliff Cameron Outgoing Correspondence, August 29, 1946-March 23, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 19)
      - Cliff Cameron to James Matles Regarding Factionalism with August 23, 1946, Executive Board Resolution, August 29, 1946; 1.
      - Cameron to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 475 Klett Manufacturing Strike, August 29, 1946; 2.
      - Cameron to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, October 15-21, 1946; 3-4.
      - Cameron to Emspak Regarding Shop Delegates Conference, October 28, 1946; 5.
      - Cameron to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Shop Delegates Conference, October 28, 1946; 6.
      - Cameron to James Matles Regarding Shop Delegates Conference, October 28, 1946; 7.
      - Cameron to Emspak Regarding PAC, October 30-November 4, 1946; 8-9.
      - Cameron to Matles Regarding Staff Members, March 3, 1947; 10.
      - Cameron to Matles Regarding Education, April 10, 1947; 11.
      - Cameron to Matles Regarding Finances, August 28, 1947; 12.
      - Cameron to Matles Regarding Staff Members, March 15, 1949; 13.
      - Cameron to Matles Regarding Local 475 Burndy Strike, March 18, 1949; 14.
      - Cameron to Matles Regarding Annual Dance, June 3, 1949; 15.
      - Cameron to Matles Regarding Finances, July 1, 1949; 16.
      - Cameron to Matles Regarding Annual Outing with Tickets, August 19, 1949; 17.
      - Cameron to Emspak Regarding Annual Outing, August 19, 1949; 18.
      - Cameron to Fitzgerald Regarding Annual Outing, August 19, 1949; 19.
    - Local 475 Cliff Cameron Outgoing Correspondence, March 23, 1950-August 15, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      - Cliff Cameron to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Annual Dance with Tickets, March 23, 1950; 1.
      - Cameron to James Matles Regarding Annual Dance, March 23, 1950; 2.
      - Cameron to Julius Emspak Regarding Annual Dance, March 23, 1950; 3.
      - Cameron to Matles Regarding Mailing List, April 7, 1950; 4.
      - Cameron to Emspak Regarding Local 475 Sklar Strike, April 19-May 23, 1950; 5-10.
      - Cameron to Matles Regarding Annual Outing, August 21, 1950; 11.
      - Cameron to Emspak Regarding Annual Outing, August 21, 1950; 12.
      - Cameron to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 475 Strike with Invitation, June 5, 1951; 13.
      - Cameron to Emspak Regarding Local 475 Strike, June 5, 1951; 14.
      - Cameron to Fitzgerald Regarding Annual Boat Ride, August 21, 1950; 15.
      - Cameron to Matles Regarding Local 475 Strike, June 5, 1951; 16.
      - Cameron to Emspak Regarding Annual Outing with Tickets, August 15, 1951; 17.
      - Cameron to Russ Nixon Regarding Annual Outing, August 15, 1951; 18.
      - Cameron to Fitzgerald Regarding Annual Outing, August 15, 1951; 19.
    - Local 475 Cliff Cameron Outgoing Correspondence, January 14, 1952-July 21, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 21)
      - Cliff Cameron to James Matles Regarding 475 News, January 14, 1952; 1.
      - Cameron to Matles Regarding Annual Report, January 31, 1952; 2.
      - Cameron to Julius Emspak Regarding Wages and Political Action, February 1, 1952; 3.
      - Cameron to All Shop Chairmen Regarding 475 News and Local 475 Strikes, June 17, 1952; 4.
      - Cameron to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Stewards Conference and Factionalism, November 4, 1952; 5.
      - Cameron to Matles Regarding Stewards Conference, November 4, 1952; 6.
      - Cameron to Emspak Regarding Stewards Conference, November 4, 1952; 7.
      - Cameron to Matles Regarding Finances and International Harvester Strikes, December 15, 1952; 8.
      - Cameron to Matles Regarding Local 475 Officers, January 7, 1953; 9.
      - Cameron to Fitzgerald, November 24, 1954; 10.
      - Cameron to Matles Regarding Local 475 Strikes and Per Capita, March 31, 1955; 11.
      - Cameron to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and Strikes, July 21, 1955; 12.
    - Local 475 Cliff Cameron Outgoing Correspondence, August 11, 1955-February 24, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      - Cliff Cameron to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 475 Strikes, August 11, 1955; 1.
      - Cameron to James Matles Regarding IUE and United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, August 11, 1955; 2.